http://www.omakchronicle.com/site/privacy.html

E-edition
This privacy notice discloses the practices for all the products, services and websites offered by Omak Chronicle. Omak-Okanogan County Chronicle LLC values your privacy and your right to your personal information.This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. Content on this site such as stories, media and advertisements, may include links to outside websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of those external sites. This policy serves to notify you of our policies and practices in the following areas:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and how it may be shared.Choices you may make regarding the use of your data.Procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to third parties. We reserve the right to use information provided by you to respond to you regarding requests, such as following up on submissions, subscriptions, or account troubleshooting. Our sites use Google Analytics to collect traffic data (ie, which web pages are the most popular or see the most activity) and basic demographics/geo location from users (user age groups, user gender, metro area location). None of this data can or may be used to specifically identify a user. If you wish to opt out from Google Analytic tracking on our website or any other, please visit the Google Analytics Opt Out page for more information on opting out of Google Analytics tracking: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information which does identify individual users, such as the number of users who searched for a particular story, number of site visitors on specific dates, or how many users interacted with a specific advertising campaign, for example.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience of our site and to serve content and advertisements relevant to you.These cookies may be used to target and serve advertisements from third party advertisers on our site. These advertisers may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our site and other websites to provide advertisements that may be of interest to you.We employ Google Doubleclick for Publisher Small Business (also known as Google Ad Manager and Google DFP) to display direct sold and third-party advertisements via ad networks.  Non-personal information may be sent to Google DFP based on your browser’s activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you. Google may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display for third party advertising. To learn more about how Google DFP uses this information, or to opt out of providing cookies to Google, visit: https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads.There are options available to you to opt out of receiving targeted advertisements, both on our site, and on others.  If you would like more information about ad targeting practices and your choices about opting out of receiving targeted ads, visit one of the following links:  http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/ or http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site and cannot be used to personally identify you. If you do not wish to browse the site with cookies, leave this site, and then clear your browser cache via your browser’s settings.Access and RegistrationTo use certain areas of this website, a user must first register with a website account. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address and contact information). This information may be used to contact you as needed. Upon registration, if you wish, you may sign up for newsletters or text messages from this site. These allow us to contact you with the latest news and offers pertaining to this site and may also contain offers and messages from our advertisers. You may opt out of these messages at any time using your account preferences. Unless you ask us not to, we may use your registration information to contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Contests, Surveys, and Optional SubmissionsFrom time-to-time our site requests information for surveys or contests or submission forms. Participation in these surveys or contests and use of these submission forms is completely voluntary and you may choose to participate and therefore disclose identifiable information. Information requested may include contact information (such as email address, phone number and name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. During registration for contests you may be asked if you are interested in signing up for offers and newsletters. You may opt out of these offers and newsletters at any time. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.Your Access To, and Control Over, Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you that is associated with your website account.Express any concern you have about our use of your data. Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy or have any questions about this policy, please contact us in writing at:Omak-Okanogan County Chronicle, LLC.PO Box 553Omak WA 98841    Changes, Modifications, and UpdatesThis Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit written consent, and most changes will be minor. Any Policy changes will be posted on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
Top Jobs
ADMINISTRATIVE SECRETARY
CORRECTIONS OFFICERS
BUS DRIVER MANSFIELD SCHOOL DISTRICT
PARA-EDUCATOR MANSFIELD SCHOOL DISTRICT
MAINTENANCE AND GROUNDS MANSFIELD SCHOOL DISTRICT
PATIENT CARE ASSOCIATE POSITION
LAB TECHNICIAN/TECHNOLOGIST
Commented
ArticlesNoma announces his resignationNorth Valley deaths rise to 15Confluence Health: ‘The hospital is full’Historic Okanogan restaurant fined by L&IMan arrested after standoff with officersRetrial finds man guilty of child rapeTwo die in separate weekend house firesAmended charges sought in murder caseMary Lees celebrates centennial birthdayMan arrested after police chase
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
© Copyright 2020 Omak-Okanogan County Chronicle, 618 Okoma Drive Omak, WA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
